wheebox.com 2016-04-04

# Online Assessment Company | Talent test | Career guidance | Wheebox

Wheebox-Web-based and Hybrid Efficient Examination Box is India’s leading talent assessment company helping Enterprise, Government and Academic Institutions globally to measure and identify talent. At Wheebox we understand that finding the right talent is the overarching initiative that supports organizational growth and stability. 

Your privacy is important at Wheebox,So we've developed a Privacy Policy that covers how we collect, use, disclose, transfer, and store your information. 

Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices and contact if you have any questions.Collection and Use of Personal information data that can be used to uniquely identify or contact a single person. You are asked to provide your personal information to sign Up at Wheebox. Here are some examples of the types of personal information WHEEBOX may collect and how we may use it.

How we use your personal information.

The personal information we collect allows us to keep you posted on Wheebox latest product announcements, updates, and upcoming events. It also helps us to improve our services, content, and advertising.

We also use personal information to help us develop, deliver, and improve our products, services, content, and advertising. We may also use personal information for internal purposes such as auditing, data analysis, and research to improve Wheebox products, services, and customer communications.

If you enter into a sweepstake, contest, or similar promotion we may use the information you provide to administer those programs.Disclosure to Third Parties at times Wheebox may make certain personal information available to strategic partners that work with WHEEBOX to provide products and services, or that help WHEEBOX market to customers. For example, when you subscribe and activate your Wheebox account, you authorize Wheebox and its carrier to exchange the information you provide during the activation process to carry out delivery service. If you are approved for service, your account will be governed by Wheebox and its delivery partners respective privacy policies. Personal information will only be shared by WHEEBOX to provide or improve our products, services and advertising; it will not be shared with third parties for their marketing purposes.

Others It may be necessary - by law, legal process, litigation, and/or requests from public and governmental authorities within or outside your country of residence - for WHEEBOX to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for purposes of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary or appropriate. Protection of Personal Information WHEEBOX takes precautions - including administrative, technical, and physical measures - to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

Integrity and Retention of Personal Information.

WHEEBOX makes it easy for you to keep your personal information accurate, complete, and up to date. We will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law. Our Companywide Commitment to Your Privacy To make sure your personal information is secure, we communicate our privacy and security guidelines to Wheebox employees and strictly enforce privacy safeguards within the company by an email or updates by email of any change in the privacy policy.

Privacy Questions.

If you have questions or concerns about WHEEBOX Privacy Policy or data processing, please contact us at

info@wheebox.com
